School of Engineering and Applied Science Records, 1884-2017: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Dean of the School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1896-2016 September 13; 149.37 linear feet 121 boxes Digital Folders: 97, Digital Files: 2,135 73,438 email messages
  - Subseries 1C: Robert G. Jahn, 1960-2003; 10.2 linear feet 11 boxes
    - Alphabetical Correspondence and Subject Files, 1966-1987; 9 boxes
      - Teem, John M., dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 187)
      - Thermionics, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 187)
      - Trustees, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Unidentified Flying Objects (Requests from Students), dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - UFOs (Requests) [from binder], dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - University Research Board, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - University Research Board, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - University Research Board [from binder], dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Study of Plasma Physics Laboratory [from binder], dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - The Use of Time in University Governance, Final Report, 9/75, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Alexander von Humboldt Foundation, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Wei-Chang, Prof. Tsien, Chinese Scientific Delegate: December 1, 1972 visit, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Women, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Women Recruiting, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Wood, Ann Douglas, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Women and Minority Engineering Students Roster, February 1975. Eng. Manpower Commission, 2 copies, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Woodrow Wilson School, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Wright, Thomas H., University Counsel, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Dorodnitzyn, A.A. (USSR) Director, Computer Center, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Zhurin, V.V. (Dr.), dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Ziolkowski, Theodore, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Electrical Engineering, J.D. Ullman, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Engineering Education, Robert G. Jahn, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Parametric Pumping, N.H. Sweed, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Plasmas, Robert G. Jahn and Lab., Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Polymers, J.K. Gillham, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Polymers, Bryce Maxwell, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Polymers, Garth L. Wilkes, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Soils, Werner E. Schmid, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Technology, E.H. Dowell, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Technology, F.C. Moon, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Systems, A.L. Kornhauser, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Systems, J.M. Lutin, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Waste Treatment, David F. Ollis, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Water Resources, G.F. Pinder, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Water Resources, Robert W. Cleary, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Systems, Margaret F. Fels, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Transportation Systems, Arnold D. Kerr, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 188)
      - Electrical Engineering, P. Mark, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Electrical Engineering, Kenneth Stieglitz, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Bioengineering, Garth L. Wilkes, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Chemical Engineering, Leon Lapidus, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Transportation Technology, Larry Sweet, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Combustion, F.V. Bracco, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Combustion, I. Glassman, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Combustion, W.A. Sirignano, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Bioengineering, T. Pavlidis, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Bioengineering, B.S.H. Royce, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Bioengineering, David F. Ollis, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Electrical Engineering, Bede Liu, Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - SEAS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1982-1986, portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Dean's Cabinet Minutes, 1978-, 1978-1986; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Minutes of Faculty Business Meetings, Dean R.G. Jahn, C230 Eng. Quad., 1971-1981; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Dean's Cabinet Minutes, 1971-, 1971-1978; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Advisory and Resource Council [membership lists, notes, meeting minutes, reports], 1975-1981; portion of 1 box (Box 189)
      - Talks, Other Authors, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Data Interior, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Data, Exterior, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Propaganda, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Freshmen, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Graduate Programs, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Faculty, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - AMS, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Ch. E., dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - CGE, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - E.E., dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Environmental Center, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Enrollments, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Basic Engineering, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Topical Programs, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Bio-Engineering, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Energy Conversion and Resources, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Transportation, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Environmental Studies, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Women, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Trustees, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - NASA Contract, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Sloan Foundation, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Minorities, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Germany, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Near East, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Food, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Thermionics, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Consulting, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Consulting--TRW, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
      - Policy, dates not examined; portion of 1 box (Box 190)
    - Robert Jahn's Talks, Articles, Publications and Related Correspondence, 1960-1989; 1 box
      - "Reflection and Transmission of Electromagnetic Waves at Electron Density Gradients", 1960; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Plasma Physics conference programs, 1966, 1969; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Robert Jahn papers and publications, 1973-1976; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications, binder 1, 1967-1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications, binder 1, 1967-1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications, binder 2, 1977-1980; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications, binder 3, 1975-1982; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications, binder 3, 1975-1982; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Copies of "Research", 1975, 1978; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - "Research", 1980; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Articles, Publications, and Related Correspondence, 1972; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks and Articles, 1973; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - "Three Eras of Engineering Education", 1973-1974; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - "The Problem of 'Drift' in University Research", 1973-1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Articles and Related Correspondence, 1974; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Minority education in engineering, 1974-1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Articles, Publications, and Related Correspondence, 1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - "Technology's Tightening Grip", 1975; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Talks, Articles, Publications and Correspondence, 1976-1977; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Reports and Plans, 1980-1984; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Princeton Engineer, 1971-1974; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
      - Princeton Engineer, 1975-1989; portion of 1 box (Box 191)
    - Ceremonial Documents, 1973-1980; 1 box
      - Bachelor of Science in Engineering Diploma, 1974; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Class Day, 1973; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Tau Beta Pi, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Energy Research Laboratory Dedication, 1980; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - DVD Recordings of Professor Robert G. Jahn's Last Four Lectures, 2003; AR.2016.128; 1 folder (Box 100, Folder 5)
      Consists of four DVD recordings of the last four lectures given Professor Robert G. Jahn in April of 2003 for the team-taught course Human/Machine Interactions (PSY/ORF322).
  - Subseries 1D: Hisashi Kobayashi, 1896-1993; 27.5 linear feet 22 boxes
    The Hisashi Kobayashi subseries documents the deanship of Hisashi Kobayashi, who returned to his alma mater, Princeton, in 1986 to serve as dean of the School of Engineering until 1991. The records consist primarily of correspondence and subject files.
    Arranged by form, and chronologically or alphabetically thereunder.
    - Correspondence, 1986 June 17-1990 December 17; 3 boxes
      - 1989 March-1989 April, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 1)
      - 1989 January-1989 February, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 2)
      - 1988 September-1988 December, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 3)
      - 1988 July-1988 August, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - 1988 May-1988 June, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - 1988 February-1988 April, 1 folder (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - 1990 September 18-1990 December 17, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - 1990 January 2-1990 March 2, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - 1990 March 5-1990 May 7, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 3)
      - 1989 October-1989 December, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - 1989 September-1989 October, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - 1989 July-1989 August, 1 folder (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - 1987 October-1988 January, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - 1986 June 17-1986 September 30, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - 1986 October 1-1986 December 31, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - 1987 May 1-1987 September 30, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - 1987 January 1-1987 April 30, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - 1990 May 8-1990 June 26, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - 1990 June 28-1990 September 17, 1 folder (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Books and Publications, 1896-1976; 2 boxes
      - The First Three Books of Homer's Iliad, 1896; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 1)
      - High School Algebra, 1906; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 2)
      - Gurley's Manual, 1904; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 3)
      - Cambria Steel Handbook, 1901; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 4)
      - The First Four Books of Xenophon's Anabasis, 1896; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 5)
      - Gillespie's Surveying, 1899; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 6)
      - The Materials of Construction, 1901; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Sewerage, 1903; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 8)
      - A Treatise on Masonry Construction, 1901; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 9)
      - Design of Simple Roof Trusses in Wood and Steel, 1903; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 10)
      - New Plane and Spherical Geometry, 1899; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 11)
      - Reservoirs for Irrigation Water-Power and Domestic Water-Supply, 1902; 1 folder (Box 104, Folder 12)
      - Theoretical and Practical Graphics, 1898; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - The Princeton Bric-a-Brac - Junior Class of Princeton University, Class of, 1903; 1902; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - Treatise on Hydraulics, 1902; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - New Plane and Spherical Trigonometry, 1896; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 4)
      - International Library of Technology, 1902-1905; 3 folders
        - International Textbook Company, 39, 1903; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 5)
        - International Textbook Company, 12B, 1905; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 6)
        - International Textbook Company, 22, 1902; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 7)
      - Field Engineering Handbook, 1901; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 8)
      - Trautwine's Engineer's Pocket-Book, 1902; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 9)
      - Analytic Mechanics, 1900; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 10)
      - Elementary Solid Geometry and Mensuration, 1896; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 11)
      - Handbook of Water Control, 1936; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 12)
      - Differential and Integral Calculus, 1898; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 13)
      - A History of the Engineering School of Princeton University (1875-1955), 1962; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Princeton University in the American Revolution, 1976; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 15)
      - Official Register of Princeton University, 1960 November-1962 October 1; 2 folders
        - Undergraduate Education at Princeton, Volume LIV, No. 3, 1962 October 1; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 16)
        - Graduate Education at Princeton, Volume LII, No. 4, 1960 November 1; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 17)
      - The Princeton University Faculty, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 18)
      - Graduate Education at Princeton, 1945-1958; 1 folder (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Subject Files, 1984-1993; 12 boxes
      - American Electronics, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Awards: Presidential Faculty Fellows, 1991; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Center for Energy and Environmental Studies, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 3)
      - Chemical Engineering, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Christmas, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - 'A' Miscellaneous, 1991; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 7)
      - Committee on the Course of Study, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 8)
      - Civil Engineering, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 9)
      - Consortium: Engineering Research Council for Surface Processing, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 10)
      - Courtyard Committee, 1991-1992; 2 folders
        - 1992, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 11)
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 12)
      - Dean of the Faculty, 1990; 2 folders
        - Gunning, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 13)
        - Numbered Memos, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 14)
      - Faculty Meetings - School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 15)
      - Freshman Parents' Day, 1990-1991; 2 folders
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 16)
        - 1990, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 17)
      - Gift Notification, 1990-1991; 2 folders
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 18)
        - 1990, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 19)
      - Higher Education and National Affairs, 1991; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 20)
      - Incubator Space, 1990-1991; 2 folders
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 21)
        - 1990, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 22)
      - Dean's Cabinet, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 23)
      - Presidential Report, 1990; 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 24)
      - Invoices, 1989-1990; 2 folders
        - 1990, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 25)
        - 1989, 1 folder (Box 106, Folder 26)
      - Dean of the Faculty, 1989; more than 2 folders
        - Robert Gunning, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 1)
        - 1989, 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 2 to 3)
      - Dean's Staff, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Development Office, 1986-1989; 3 folders
        - 1989, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 5)
        - 1988, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 6)
        - 1986-1987, 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 7)
      - Dryer, Frederick, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 107, Folder 8 to 10)
      - 'E' Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 11 to 12)
      - Earthquake, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 13)
      - Education, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 107, Folder 14 to 15)
      - Electrical Engineering, 1986-1989; 4 folders (Box 107, Folder 16 to 19)
      - Engineering Biology, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 20)
      - Engineering Foundation Grants, 1987; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 21)
      - Engineering Liberal Arts, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 22)
      - Enrollment, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 107, Folder 23 to 25)
      - Equipment Notes, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 26)
      - 'F' Miscellaneous, 1987-1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 27)
      - Faculty, 1986-1989; 4 folders
        - Candidates, 1989; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 28)
        - Committee on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1987; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 29)
        - General, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 30)
        - Meetings, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 31)
      - Fauchet, Phillipe, 1988; 1 folder (Box 107, Folder 32)
      - Fellowships, 1986-1989; 5 folders
        - 1989, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 1)
        - 1988, 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 2)
        - 1986-1987, 3 folders
          - Ash, David W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 3)
          - Blum, Avrim L., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 4)
          - Zuckerman, David I., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 5)
      - Fitzmorris, Charles C, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 108, Folder 6 to 8)
      - Forward Planning, 1987 April; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 9)
      - Foundation Relations, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 108, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Fuchs, Ira, 1989; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 12)
      - Fund Raising, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 108, Folder 13 to 15)
      - International Business Machines (IBM), 1986-1989; more than 4 folders
        - Grant, 1986; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 16)
        - Japan, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 108, Folder 17 to 18)
        - Princeton, Summary Reports, 1988; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 19)
        - University, 1986; 1 folder (Box 108, Folder 20)
      - Interactive Computer Graphics Laboratory, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 108, Folder 21 to 23)
      - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers Incorporated, 1986-1989; more than 2 folders
        - 1986-1989, 3 folders (Box 109, Folder 1 to 3)
        - Hamming Award, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 109, Folder 4 to 6)
      - Nomination, 1985-1989; 12 folders
        - Iwadare Yoshiroro, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 7)
        - Doctor Joseph Raviv, 1989; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 8)
        - Resier, Martin, 1985-1987; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 9)
        - 1987, 8 folders
          - Belady, Laszlo, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 10)
          - Darringer, John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 11)
          - Jaffe, Jeffrey, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 12)
          - Lam, Simon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 13)
          - Lavenberg, Stephan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 14)
          - Mark, Jon Wei, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 15)
          - Peled, Abraham, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 16)
          - Yu, Philips, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 17)
      - Incubator Space, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 109, Folder 18 to 20)
      - Information Technology Research, 1989; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 21)
      - Invoices, 1988; 1 folder (Box 109, Folder 22)
      - Kobayashi, Hisashi, 1986-1989; more than 3 folders
        - Vitae, Bio, Etc, 1987; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 1)
        - Personal, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 2 to 3)
        - Travel Vouchers, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 4)
      - 'L' Miscellaneous, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 5 to 6)
      - Lehigh University, 1989; 2 folders
        - Advisory Council, 1989; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 7)
        - Computer Science and Electrical Engineering Visiting Committee, 1989 March 28-29; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 8)
      - Library, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 110, Folder 9 to 11)
      - 'M' Miscellaneous, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 12)
      - Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 110, Folder 13 to 15)
      - Manufacturing Research, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 110, Folder 16)
      - Materials Science, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 110, Folder 17 to 18)
      - 'J' Miscellaneous, 1986-1989; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Jackson, Allison L, 1989; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 3)
      - Jahn, Bob, 1989; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 4)
      - Japan, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 5 to 7)
      - Japan Address List, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 8)
      - Japanese Corporations, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 9 to 11)
      - Japanese Computer Technology, 1987; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 12)
      - Japanese Subsidiaries in New Jersey, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 13)
      - Japan Productivity Center, 1989; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 14)
      - Japan Society, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 15 to 16)
      - Japanese Universities, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 17 to 19)
      - 'K' Miscellaneous, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 111, Folder 20)
      - Kajima, 1987-1989; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 21 to 23)
      - Kobayashi, 1986-1989; more than 2 folders
        - Activities, 1986-1989; 3 folders (Box 111, Folder 24 to 26)
        - Vitae, Bio, Etc, 1988-1989; 2 folders (Box 111, Folder 27 to 28)
      - Kajima, 1990; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 1)
      - Hishashi's Reception, 1991 June 4; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 2)
      - Jackson, Allison L, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1990; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 5)
      - Wilkes University, 1991; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 6)
      - Vacation Record, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 7 to 8)
      - X-Ray Lasers, 1990; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 9)
      - University Research Board, 1990-1993; 3 folders
        - General, 1990; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 10)
        - 1991, 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 11)
        - Miscellaneous - Memoranda, Meetings, Correspondence, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 12)
      - Invoices, 1991; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 13)
      - Kajima, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 14)
      - University Faculty Meetings, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 112, Folder 15 to 16)
      - Undergraduate Labs, 1990; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 17)
      - 'U' Miscellaneous, 1991; 1 folder (Box 112, Folder 18)